<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Deb]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Deb]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/deb/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 00:44:24 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/deb/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/d39d241f-b404-4e08-acca-e3ce5ee02bdb.png">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/deb/324e6777-3ec5-41e9-9163-2276a8935fcb/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">324e6777-3ec5-41e9-9163-2276a8935fcb</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 00:43:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="http://www.debsnyder.me/uploads/6/0/8/0/6080466/1461024449.png">]]></description>
            <link>http://www.debsnyder.me/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">714a8220-bcde-438f-b79a-8b656e7da527</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 00:43:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="http://www.debsnyder.me/uploads/6/0/8/0/6080466/3074214_orig.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/deb/69722a38-e907-4584-8767-e7f4668ba8f4/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">69722a38-e907-4584-8767-e7f4668ba8f4</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 00:43:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="http://www.debsnyder.me/uploads/6/0/8/0/6080466/6248220_orig.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>http://www.debsnyder.me/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3024ca04-c19d-4be9-8aae-2e1aacc11ab6</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 00:43:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="http://www.debsnyder.me/uploads/6/0/8/0/6080466/8240019.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/deb/51a068cb-49e0-4955-80cd-a8c1a6f268ad/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">51a068cb-49e0-4955-80cd-a8c1a6f268ad</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 00:43:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Deb starred in the Ang Lee film (Pushing Hands), and has worked with such greats as Sydney Pollack, Harrison Ford and George Clooney. She appeared in numerous television commercials (Disney, Wendy’s, Febreze and AARP) and on many TV shows including Boston Legal, Unscripted and General Hospital. She originated several characters for playwright Nicky Silver while making her Off-Broadway debut. Deb Snyder is a gifted writer of children's music, plays, books and shows. She collaborates with Phillip Bynoe as the group, PBnDeb, to create original songs dealing with the everyday issues and joys of childhood. They completed their first album, “Growing Up” in 2006, a songwriter’s compilation. They released their second album “Zoo Dance” in 2008. “Zoo Dance” is an interactive pop record enjoyed by kids from one to six and their parents. The music invites all who listen to sing, dance, act and even count bugs... loudly. As a teacher, she undertook the challenge of writing and directing plays for children, aged 8-16, for presentation at the Charles River Creative Arts Park in MA, the Freelance Players in MA, and the University of Miami in FL. She recently taught an on-camera audition class for children at Deborah Gibson's Camp Electric Youth in Hollywood, CA. Deb worked at Walker/Fitzgibbon TV & Films as Head of Development and Production. As an award-winning writer, director, producer and actor, Deb brings valuable insight from both sides of the camera to the company. She gained experience at Echo Bridge, a top production company based in Boston, Massachusetts, by working on several award-winning documentaries, a feature film (Landfall) and a boating reality pilot presentation (At Nine Knots) that took her up and down the New England Coast as the host and a producer. Desiring to expand her talents as a creative executive, she relocated to California and began working in development, script evaluation, research, writing treatments and pitching shows to networks for Nasser Entertainment. As writer, director and producer, Deb captured the 'Grand Prize' in the Indie No Budget Film Competition entitled, “Historically Speaking”' by innovatively breaking the rules to create the winning film, “CarouCell”. Her film went on to garner an 'Honorable Mention' at the Louis Wolfson II Media History Center Film and Video Awards, a worldwide competition. Deb received a BA in Liberal Arts from Kalamazoo College in Kalamzoo, Michigan and a Master’s Degree in Theater from Brandeis University in Waltham, Massachusetts. Additionally, she studied theater at the British European Studies Group in London.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/deb/deb-starred-in-the-ang-lee-film-pushing-hands-and-has-wor/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44b964dd-e694-422d-b67e-241a6888490d</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 00:43:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>